<resources>
    <string name="app_name">SharedElementTransition</string>
    <string name="deer_description">Deer are fascinating creatures! They\'re known for their grace and agility, often seen bounding effortlessly through forests and meadows. Did you know there are about 47 species of deer found throughout the world? They vary in size, color, and habitat preferences. From the majestic red deer of Europe to the tiny pudu of South America, each species has its own unique characteristics.</string>
    <string name="monkey_description">The monkey, a small to medium-sized primate, swings through trees with agility and intelligence. With a variety of colors and sizes, monkeys live in social troops and enjoy playing together. They are omnivores, eating fruits, vegetables, insects, and small animals. Found in tropical and subtropical regions, monkeys add charm and liveliness to their surroundings.</string>
    <string name="tiger_description">The tiger is the largest cat species and a majestic predator found in various habitats across Asia. With its striking black stripes against a vibrant orange coat, the tiger exudes both power and beauty. Known for its strength and hunting prowess, this magnificent animal commands respect and awe. Tigers are solitary creatures, marking their territory and roaming vast areas in search of prey. Their stealthy nature and sharp senses make them formidable hunters, capable of taking down large animals like deer, wild boar, and even crocodiles. Tigers play a crucial role in maintaining the balance of their ecosystems, ensuring the health and diversity of their habitats.</string>
    <string name="lion_description">The lion, often referred to as the "King of the Jungle," is a majestic and powerful big cat found in various regions of Africa. With its striking mane and muscular build, the lion exudes an aura of strength and authority. As apex predators, lions play a crucial role in maintaining the balance of their ecosystems. They are highly social animals, living in prides that consist of related females, their offspring, and a few males. Lions are known for their impressive hunting skills, working together to take down prey much larger than themselves. Their powerful jaws and sharp claws make them formidable predators. The lion\'s distinctive roar, which can be heard from miles away, is a symbol of their presence and dominance.</string>
    <string name="elephant_description">The elephant, the largest land animal, roams the savannas and forests of Africa and Asia with grace and power. Known for its immense size, long trunk, and tusks, the elephant is a symbol of strength, wisdom, and longevity. These gentle giants are highly social and live in close-knit family groups led by experienced matriarchs. Elephants are herbivores and spend a significant portion of their day foraging for food, using their trunks to grasp vegetation and draw water. Their intelligence and problem-solving abilities are remarkable, and they exhibit complex social behaviors such as mourning their dead and caring for their young. Elephants play a crucial role in maintaining their ecosystems by shaping habitats and dispersing seeds.</string>
</resources>